* * *

To review our [DMCA policy](https://controlc.com/contact/) or to request a paste be deleted, [click here](https://controlc.com/contact/)  

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* * *

Web Site Terms and Conditions of Use
------------------------------------

You can reach us with any questions at **[\[email protected\]](https://controlc.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)**  

### 1\. Terms

By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.

### 2\. Use License

Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on ControlC's web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:

* modify or copy the materials;
* use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);
* attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on ControlC's web site;
* remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
* transfer the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials on any other server.

This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by ControlC at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.

### 3\. Disclaimer

The materials on ControlC's web site are provided "as is". ControlC makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, ControlC does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.

### 4\. Limitations

In no event shall ControlC or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on ControlC's Internet site, even if ControlC or a ControlC authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage.  
  
While ControlC will make best efforts to ensure the availability and security of the website and user data, users acknowledge and agree that ControlC shall not be held liable for any unauthorized access, modification, distribution or deletion of user data, whether temporary or permanent. Users are strongly advised to maintain their own copies of all data submitted to the website and understand that they are solely responsible for safeguarding their data. ControlC disclaims any liability for any loss, damage, or inconvenience resulting from data incidents and encourages users to take appropriate precautions to protect their information.

### 5\. Revisions and Errata

The materials appearing on ControlC's web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. ControlC does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. ControlC may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. ControlC does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.

### 6\. Suspensions and Banning

ControlC reserves the right to ban or suspend any user at its discretion if they violate these Terms of Service. In such cases, all user data may be deleted, any owed payments forfeited, and access to the website terminated without notice. These actions are solely determined by ControlC, and ControlC is not liable for any resulting consequences.

### 7\. Site Terms of Use Modifications

ControlC may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.

### 8\. Governing Law

Any claim relating to ControlC's web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of Florida without regard to its conflict of law provisions.

### 9\. Paste data collection and privacy

Any data you post to ControlC may be publicly visible and remain forever.

### 10\. License for Submitted Content

By submitting any content to our site, you grant us an exclusive, worldwide, irrevocable, royalty-free license to use, reproduce, adapt, modify, publish, distribute, publicly perform, and publicly display the Content in any manner and for any purpose, including but not limited to marketing, promotion, and advertising, without any further consent or compensation to you. This license shall remain in effect unless and until you or ControlC removes the content from our website.

### 12\. Acceptable content

You agree that you will not post information or link to any information that is libelous, nor may it promote hate, violence, or illegal activity in any country. You may not impersonate any individual or group, real or fictitious, if asked to provide personally identifying information. You may not use this website for any purpose which would be deemed illegal under united states law. You agree that you will not hold ControlC or its operators responsible for any damages that may result from direct or indirect usage of this website, or for any other operations of this website. You acknowledge that there is no guarantee as to the suitability of this website for any specific purpose. The Terms of Service may change at any time without notification.  
  
In addition, You agree that you will not post any content that contains, or contains links to:  
  
\* unlawful content or content that promotes unlawful activities  
\* email or password lists  
\* content that infringes on any proprietary right of any party, including patent, trade secret, copyright, or any others.  
\* Financial data, including but not limited to credit card numbers or banking details  
\* Personally identifiable information or "dox"  
\* Pornographic content  
\* Exploits, Malware, Viruses or any form of 'command and control' information which is used by malware  
\* Threats, Harassment, Libel/Slander, Scams, Blackmail, Discrimination or Racism  
\* Any other material which is not legal, both civilly or criminally in the United States of America  

### 13\. Right to remove user content

We reserve the right to reject, delete or remove any content we deem unacceptable, in our sole discretion, without restriction.

### 14\. Survivability:

In the event that any provision or part of this Terms of service is determined to be unenforceable by a court of competent jurisdiction, the remaining provisions of this contract shall continue to be valid and enforceable to the fullest extent permitted by law, and the unenforceable provision shall be modified or reformed to the extent necessary to make it enforceable while preserving the parties' original intent to the greatest extent possible.

### 15\. Automated Access:

Access to this website through automated means, such as bots, crawlers, or any other form of software or technology, is expressly forbidden without the pre-authorized consent of the website owner. Unauthorized automated access may result in the immediate termination of access and legal action. To request permission for automated access, please contact [\[email protected\]](https://controlc.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Privacy Policy
--------------

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

* Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we may identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
* We may collect and use of personal information, unless as required by law.
* We may retain personal information indefinitely.
* Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
* We may protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
* We may make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
